Fushi learns of Gugu's daily struggles as Hiro tells him about the life he now leads
and how Gugu's feelings for Takunaha still run deep.
I felt like I still had memories to make in Takunaha. I wasn't done yet.
No matter how much of a paradise you turn this place into, you can't remove people's troubles, doubts, or anguish.
After all, we're only human.
In a lonely night, we're asking for help.
Can I help you?
Can I help you with yourself?
The voice of the heart is ringing.
Let me tell you, let me tell you, let me tell you.
終わらない想いを繰り返し秘密の彼方へ
不安から遠ざかる術はどこにあるのか見えないまま
誰かが変わってくれたなら
それで救われるのか
不滅のあなたへ叫びたい
夢動く代わりに歌いたい
言葉と言葉を重ねて
秘密の彼方へ
秘密世界中
Hey, Goo Goo, I can help you with that.
Oh, awesome.
Thank you.
Huh?
I can do it.
I got it.
Ushii, looks like you're in a good mood today.
Mmm.
Hey, do you think I'm being silly?
I've been trying to get on everyone's good side because I'm worried they'll all leave
me.
Was that a you got me?
Or were you laughing at me?
Maybe I'm being crazy for feeling like there's no point in being alive without them.
You know, March said something similar a long time ago.
Bon, you're back?
She said she'd be sad, having to live into adulthood without you there by her side.
She tried desperately to stop you, but you ignored her and went into a slumber to continue
your war.
Uh, yeah.
So March ingested poison to end it.
Huh?
End it?
She took her own life next to you, but she didn't suffer.
The city of Renru and its bitter war against the knockers.
There were so many casualties.
And of course, you'd lost everything too, Fushi.
Although, eventually we won.
The knockers left the city, and you continued your slumber.
Poor March.
She's just a little girl.
I know what she's going through.
It's painful to leave everything behind.
It's so hard to move on.
Now listen.
I'm the only one who has a good excuse to become a villain here.
So tell me what I can do.
If I could meet Fushi one more time, you know what I'd say?
It's not just physical pain I couldn't get.
I also couldn't understand the pains of the soul.
the pains of the soul.
Hyrule followed through with it.
So did March.
Are you leaving, Tanari?
I have to. I can't stay here any longer.
Take care of yourself.
I'm his big brother. I have to look after his grave.
Even long after you'd reacquired your vessels,
you were so deep in your slumber that you didn't even recognize us.
Toonari was tormented by guilt.
She regretted giving March the poison which had allowed her to die.
You mustn't let it trouble you. After all, you simply did what needed to be done.
Yes, I know. Still…
Please understand that I would have done exactly the same if I were in your position.
Fushi will reawaken one day.
The Church of Bennett is powerful, and so are the anti-Fushi groups.
To them, Fushi is an evil demon,
which is all the more reason to spread the word of Fushi the Savior.
Wouldn't you agree?
For the future that lies ahead for everyone.
And you're the only one of us who can do it, Tanari.
So Tanari got to work.
She wrote the legend of Fushi.
The truth of Fushi.
And then,
Hyro spread it all around the world.
However,
the anti-Fushi folks were still as aggressive as ever.
You're wrong! Fushi isn't like that!
He saved this city, and now he's fighting to save the entire world!
Silence! Get him!
Listen, don't fight them!
Don't hurt any of them!
Kamu!
That's enough!
The King of Sonya!
The throne will now administer this land directly.
None shall interfere.
Dammit, Anno, why can you never be on time, huh?
Gugu managed to protect your body, never hurting anyone.
Massar made sure to keep a watchful eye on the King of Sonya.
Although he never cared much for his own well-being,
he did bring Euralis and the nation of Sonya together.
Prince Bond!
Apologies, Baron Haramaki.
A letter from King Torta for you.
Thank you.
And through his efforts, Kai brought me and Euralis together.
Those Bennett assholes are about to find out what happens when they don't leave us alone.
I'm really hoping this is the last time we have to do battle with these people.
Let's go!
Our continuous battles against the Bennett territories waged on.
Kai and Massar were always there, right on the front lines.
Then, around the time the battles ended.
I was the last of us to join you.
Everyone was waiting for you.
For centuries.
I was the last of us to join you.
Everyone was waiting for you.
For centuries.
I was the last of us to join you.
Everyone was waiting for you, for centuries.
And now you're starting to feel that you're going to be the one left behind.
That's just not true.
Everyone is trying to live alongside you.
Here's something that will blow your immortal mind.
Who do you think it was who asked me to come back because they were worried about you?
It was Massar. Can you believe that?
And here we were, thinking he only cared about booze and girls.
Nobody here is so fed up with you that they want to leave this place.
In fact, it's quite the opposite. You must know that.
If anything, they want you to be happy. Of that, I am absolutely sure.
How many times? How many more times?
Can we eat together? Talk together? Play together?
A thousand? Maybe a hundred more times?
How many times will I get to see them again?
Plenty of times. As many as you like.
You're lying! There will definitely be a last time!
I know, because Tanari told me. She said that they're all going to die here.
I know the truth. Their only dream is to make their own dreams come true, not to spend their lives living with me forever.
Fushi. Whether it's a thousand times or just a hundred, will you ever truly be satisfied?
Even if you knew it would be the last time you were together.
I couldn't bear that.
What's this? Kid's got himself all worked up.
Hey, Fushi, are you okay?
I just wanted to call you in for dinner.
Looks like you're discussing something important.
Yeah, let's go.
Fushi, don't you think now's a good time to tell everyone here how you're feeling?
What? No way!
Hey, come on. What's up?
Um, well, let's...
Please don't... please don't die and leave me behind.
Please don't die and leave you behind? What the hell?
It's okay, Fushi. I'll always be here with you.
No, that's not what I mean, March.
Then what do you mean?
Well, for example, if you were to die one day, then as long as you stayed here with me,
I wouldn't mind bringing all of you back to life and we can keep on being happy.
Seriously?
Yeah, like it would be nice to do that. I guess that's what I really mean.
So you're asking us to keep living and dying and coming back just like you do? Forever?
I'm sorry! I am! Please don't hate me for that!
Someone help me with this, please!
You're gonna spill it!
And he's gone.
Oh, no. Everything I just said to them must have sounded so pathetic.
They'll definitely think so little of me now.
Why? Why the hell am I...
The way I am!
I guess none of them understand how I feel because they're not immortal like I am.
What did I expect?
What would they do if they were like me?
Just who am I supposed to become in this world anyway?
I mean, I should figure out who I want to become like...
Oh, did you come to get me again?
It's okay. You don't need to worry about me.
Wasn't this where...
Oh, are these all the babies from the eggs I laid?
I can't believe each one of them has a pie!
Amazing!
I'm a mom now, too!
Oh, right!
I should give you all names!
You're called Shumai,
you're Gyoza,
Ramen,
Twice Cooked Pork,
Chop Suey!
I promise I'll give you a name someday, too, horse.
Where are you going?
To the sea?
But wait!
I've only just found you!
What are you doing,
evil crabs?
Stop it!
You can't eat Shumai!
Everyone, come here!
It's too dangerous outside!
I'll protect you!
We can all go home and live together forever!
That'll be much better for you!
I'm sorry!
Please, tell me you don't hate me!
Don't hate me!
I couldn't stand it if you did!
Everyone...
was so very kind.
Right to the end!
...
I don't like a secret...
Nice to meet you!
I don't like it!
I'm sorry...
...
I'm FUNA!
Huh? Hang on! What the hell?
Oh, wow! Fushi, your new hairstyle looks great on you!
Ah, and I see Mizua is absent again.
Yeah, you can do it!
What?! Cherry Blossom viewing at the VP's house?!
Sounds good to me. Does this mean that we also get the opportunity to meet your other friends as well, Fushi?
Yeah, of course, right? Fushi?
Mm-hmm.
Looks like we're going to have quite the crowd.
Hey, you should come too.
I'd love to.
Something wrong?
Oh, um...
No, it's nothing.
Need detergent? I can get it.
Oh, not that one. Get the bottle instead.
Oh, perfect. That's the one.
You know, you're pretty good at this, Fushi.
Well, Goo Goo taught me a long time ago.
Wow, you've improved so much!
Well, let's talk about the next Bonest Award.
It's my opinion that it should go to...
Fushi sure does sleep a lot. Especially on the weekends.
Seems like he's been working really hard lately.
Tenori! The bag's ready!
Eko, why don't you join us?
We'll be back halfway with the announcements!
Hey guys, we're all getting ready to go to bed.
Okay, yeah.
By the way, Goo Goo, I wanted to give you this.
Huh?
Oh, what is it?
It's a ticket to Takunaha.
Huh? To Takunaha?
What brought this on?
How'd you manage to get it?
I saved up and bought it.
I left an empty shell here and went to earn money.
I worked at a restaurant.
You're young, but you're so good!
Wait, you worked a job and saved up all for me?
Mm-hmm. You should go during spring break.
Damn! This is so awesome, man!
I can't believe it!
Thank you so much!
Oh, crap! I can't just be standing around!
I've gotta go pack!
I wonder if our plugs will work with the outlets over there.
Hey, Fushi, you got a phone?
Uh-oh.
You should buy one.
Also, do you have any light jackets you can take?
I can lend you one of mine if you don't.
No, because...
Oh, that's right.
I guess you don't need to pack anything.
You'll be waiting for me over there.
I'm not going, Gugu.
I wanted you to be able to live over there for as long as you like.
I asked Kazumitsu and Bond to get permission from the school.
Oh.
So that's what this is.
You sure you're okay with this?
You're not gonna get all mopey again, are you?
No, I won't.
I promise, brother.
No, Hyrule.
Please don't graduate and leave us all.
Above all, don't get a girlfriend.
Hey.
Well done graduating.
I bet you're not happy graduating when you're this popular, right?
Yeah, kinda.
It was an interesting place for me, and I admit, I'm gonna miss it.
But it's not even close to how much I'm gonna miss you, Gugu.
You can cut that shit out!
You know how much I can't stand all that sentimental stuff!
Gugu!
Come on now!
He just healed!
You're gonna make sure you come back once a year, right?
But we're really going to miss you, so I think you should come back once a week instead.
Right, Fushi?
I don't think something like that's going to be very doable, March.
Really?
I tell you what, I'll do my best to come back whenever I can.
I brought more tea in case anybody wants some.
Hey there, Yuki.
Thanks so much for inviting us.
Hi, VP.
Hello and welcome, fellow Occult Club members.
Handicrafts Club.
Very nice to meet you.
I'm Hana.
Hello there.
Thank you very much for having us.
Wow, so this is the Vice President's place?
Is that horse free range?
It's a good thing the flowers bloom during spring break this year.
Perfect time, wouldn't you say?
I agree.
Hey, come sit and join us.
I'd love to.
Thanks.
Hi there.
What are you making?
Tasty... dumplings?
Yeah, tasty.
You're really good at making dumplings, aren't you?
Hey, is there something wrong?
Look at this.
My youngest child's name is Kanitaro.
Wow, what an amazing crab.
Did you raise him yourself?
Yep.
I'm his mommy.
Oh, wow.
So if you're his mom, then can I be his dad?
Oh, of course.
Come on, let's go make a house over here.
Hello.
Are you Gugu by any chance?
The VP told us all about you.
Is it true that you can breathe fire?
Ugh.
Can we have your autograph?
I wish Mizuha could be here.
She would've had fun.
I hope she's okay.
I mean, she hasn't even been to school lately, huh?
Yeah.
Nah, it's not all bad.
Sometimes absence makes the heart grow fonder.
What?
We all talking about Gugu, ain't that right?
Ah.
The Tsar, if you're going to smoke around people, then you need to learn proper etiquette.
Why don't you use this before Kazumitsu yells at you again?
Uh, what the hell is this, an ashtray?
Yep.
Wait, did you like make this or something?
Yeah, it's a gift for you.
What do you mean by that?
I'm planning on taking an apprenticeship with a blacksmith, but for now I'm going to focus on making things like these instead of swords.
Good luck, Kai.
You got this.
Ah, that's right.
Whoa!
You're really giving this to me?
Thanks so much, Masar.
That's such a nice gift.
I have something for you too, Hyro.
What?
You're giving me this bike?
Yeah.
You wanted one, right?
That's so kind of you, Masar.
Nah, I just happened to went at the horse track and did a little shopping, that's all.
Come on, I had it.
Over here.
Don't.
We'll set it, yeah.
Right.
You didn't have to see me off, you know.
Could've just stayed at home and chilled.
No way.
I couldn't have done that.
Oh, hey.
Have you ever tried these before?
Mm-mm.
They're great.
You should get Bond to buy them.
Hmph.
If I had any money, I would've bought you plenty of things.
I never got to do any Big Brother stuff for you.
It's fine, you know that.
Okay, I'm good from here, Fushi.
Mm.
We're gonna be really far apart for quite a while.
I know.
One day, we'll see each other again.
Hmph.
Ha!
Well, no kidding, right?
You can make it to Takunaha in less than ten seconds, can't you, Fushi?
Ha!
Well, anyway, for real though, you're always welcome to come hang out.
Yeah, I'll try my best to hold back though.
I feel like that's for the best.
Yeah, I get it.
I'll be rooting for you from Takunaha.
Please make your way to gate 47.
See you later.
Let me know as soon as you buy a smartphone, okay?
I'll get one now.
By the way, how do planes even fly?
I don't get it.
It looks impossible.
Scary.
I could never see myself riding in one of those things.
Weren't you afraid, Gugu?
You were scared?
You can literally turn into a bird.
You'll just have to get used to this stuff.
Who knows what kind of vehicles people will have in a hundred or a thousand years from now.
It's important to keep up with civilization.
For you and me both.
Happy birthday to me.
Happy birthday dear Mizuha.
Happy birthday.
Happy birthday birthdayל
Happy birthday
Happy birthday!
We'll be right back.